
<!DOCTYPE resources [
    <!ENTITY appname "True Sight for Dota 2">
    <!ENTITY all_roles "All">
    <!ENTITY support_role "Support">
    <!ENTITY carry_role "Carry">
    <!ENTITY jungler_role "Jungler">
    <!ENTITY off_lane_role "Off lane">
    <!ENTITY mid_role "Mid">
    <!ENTITY roaming_role "Roaming">
    ]>

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">&appname;</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="demo">Demo photo recognition</string>
    <string name="use_last_photo">Use last photo</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>

    <string name="take_photo">Take photo</string>

    <string name="picture">Picture</string>
    <string name="camera_help_text">Position the 5 enemy hero portraits to fill the box below. Ensure the colored lines above them are visible.</string>
    <string name="camera_example_text">For example:</string>
    <string name="request_permission">This app needs camera permission.</string>
    <string name="processing_image">Detecting heroes...</string>
    <string name="opening_tip">Tip: press the camera button in the top-right to use a photo instead of typing.</string>

    <string name="about_text">&appname; is free software. You can redistribute it and/or modify
        it under the terms of the GNU General Public License v3. The source code is freely
        available on github: https://github.com/dbdkmezz/true-sight-dota</string>

    <string name="about_open_cv">&appname; uses the OpenCV (Open Source Computer Vision Library)
        for image detection and image recognition. Thanks to the OpenCV team for their excellent
        library :)</string>

    <string name="dota_trademark">Dota 2 is a registered trademark of Valve Corporation. All game
        images and names are property of Valve Corporation. This app is not affiliated with Valve
        Corporation.</string>

    <string name="dota_wiki_license">Descriptions of magic immunity ability interactions is taken
        from the Dota 2 wiki, http://dota2.gamepedia.com/ This text is copyright under Creative
        Commons license CC BY-NC-SA 3.0.</string>

    <string name="counter_picker">Counter picker</string>
    <string name="hero_abilities">Hero abilities</string>
    <string name="dispells">Spell immunity</string>

    <string name="cooldown">COOLDOWN</string>
    <string name="mana_cost">MANA COST</string>
    <string name="passive">Passive ability</string>
    <string name="passive_aura">Passive aura</string>

    <string name="stuns">Stuns</string>
    <string name="no_stuns_found">No stuns found!</string>
    <string name="disables">Disables</string>
    <string name="no_disables_found">No other disables found</string>
    <string name="silences">Silences</string>
    <string name="no_silences_found">No silences found!</string>
    <string name="ultimates">Ultimates</string>
    <string name="talents">Talents</string>

    <string name="loading_counter_picker">Calculating counters...</string>

    <string name="enter_name_tip">Hero name</string>

    <string name="all_roles">&all_roles;</string>
    <string name="carry_role">&carry_role;</string>
    <string name="off_lane_role">&off_lane_role;</string>
    <string name="jungler_role">&jungler_role;</string>
    <string name="mid_role">&mid_role;</string>
    <string name="roaming_role">&roaming_role;</string>
    <string name="support_role">&support_role;</string>

    <string-array name="roles_array">
        <item>&all_roles;</item>
        <item>&carry_role;</item>
        <item>&mid_role;</item>
        <item>&off_lane_role;</item>
        <item>&support_role;</item>
        <item>&roaming_role;</item>
        <item>&jungler_role;</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="privacy_policy_content">
        <![CDATA[
<h1>PRIVACY POLICY</h1>
<p>This privacy policy governs your use of the software application True Sight for Dota 2 (&quot;Application&quot;) for mobile devices that was created by Paul Carver. The Application is a free software (GPL v3) Android app designed for use when playing Valve Corporation\'s game Dota 2. True Sight provides full information for counter picking enemy heroes, and the details of their abilities and talent choices. As well as typing the name of enemy heroes, heroes may also be identified using a photograph of the enemy team.</p>
<p>Dota 2 is a registered trademark of Valve Corporation. All game images and names in the Application are property of Valve Corporation. This Application is not affiliated with Valve Corporation.</p>

<br></br>
<h4>What information does the Application obtain and how is it used?</h4>
In order for counter picking information in the Application to be up to date the Application submits the names of the five heroes to a server operated by Paul Carver. This information may be stored on the server for up to 24 months. The names of these heroes may be generated by the Application analysing a photograph taken by the uesr.
<p>In addition the Application may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile devices unique device ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, and information about the way you use the Application. </p>

<br></br>
<h4>Does the Application collect the photographs I take when using the Application?</h4>
<p>This Application stores on your Android device the most recent photograph taken from within the Application. All processing of these photographs is done within the Application on the Android device itself. Photographs taken when using the Application do not leave the Application and are not themselves uploaded to the server which provides counter picking information.</p>

<br></br>
<h4>Does the Application collect precise real time location information of the device?</h4>
<p>This Application does not collect precise information about the location of your mobile device. </p>

<br></br>
<h4>Do third parties see and/or have access to information obtained by the Application?</h4>
<p>Only aggregated, anonymized data is periodically transmitted to external services to help us improve the Application and our service. We will share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.</p>
<p>We may disclose User Provided and Automatically Collected Information:</p>
<p>&#8226; as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process;</br>
<p>&#8226; when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request;</br>
<p>&#8226; with our trusted services providers who work on our behalf, do not have an independent use of the information we disclose to them, and have agreed to adhere to the rules set forth in this privacy statement.</br>

<br></br>
<h4>What are my opt-out rights?</h4>
<p>You can stop all collection of information by the Application easily by uninstalling the Application. You may use the standard uninstall processes as may be available as part of your mobile device or via the mobile application marketplace or network.

<br></br>
<h4>Data Retention Policy, Managing Your Information</h4>
<p>We will retain User Provided data for as long as you use the Application and for a reasonable time thereafter. We will retain Automatically Collected information for up to 24 months and thereafter may store it in aggregate. If you’d like us to delete User Provided Data that you have provided via the Application, please contact us at dbdkmezz@gmail.com and we will respond in a reasonable time.

<br></br>
<h4>Changes</h4>
<p>This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy here and informing you via email. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes, as continued use is deemed approval of all changes.</p>

<br></br>
<h4>Your Consent</h4>
<p>By using the Application, you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. &quot;Processing,&quot; means using cookies on a computer/hand held device or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in the United States and the United Kingdom. If you reside outside the United States or United Kingdom your information may be transferred, processed and stored to these countries under their privacy standards. </p>

<br></br>
<h4>Contact us</h4>
<p>If you have any questions regarding privacy while using the Application, or have questions about our practices, please contact us via email at dbdkmezz@gmail.com.</p>
    ]]>
    </string>

</resources>
